Ajay Hello Hello
everyone, today's comparison is
about Bajaj Allianz's Extra Care Plus Super Top plan versus
ICICI Lombard's subscription.
Both are general insurance companies and are
very travel companies. Super Top plan
helps a lot. Low premiums are
enough for people to choose and these people
also buy a lot. Everyone should definitely consider top plan. If we
talk about rates, subscription is
available
in Jhalawar. The option of 5 lakh to 50 lakh
is available. The dutiable amount in Jhalawar's
policy is 2 lakh, 5 lakh and 10 lakh,
whereas in this policy it is 3 lakh 45 lakh. The maximum entry up
to which a person can take a child in a month can be
purchased on top plan. The
entry in this policy is 90, whereas there is no maximum
limit. No claim bonus,
which means that the war company
video.com
This option is not available in Bajaj's policy.
Reset benefit, which means that
whatever your time is, if tomorrow  If the policy is completed then the
company settles it only once a year.
The condition is that it does not provide coverage for the disease.
This option is available in pet.
Whereas if you subscribe to hospitalization
then you can subscribe for 60 years in one company. The
cover is provided in the policies of both the companies.
Uday Singh covers diseases whereas
ICICI Lombard provides coverage after 2 years.
Emergency road ambulance. You
can avail ambulance for Rs. 3050 in Bajaj policy. Now you must
subscribe to the channel in school. You
must share this because the
charges of ambulance are not available in this ward. If we
talk about subscription then
you can pay up to Rs. 1000 for individual and Rs. 1000. You can get
their list centers and their state
quid test from them, you
can get cashless tricycle test done every year. If we talk about typing then there is no such thing
in Bajaj policy.
After this year you
can make payment at 20 per cent. If you have taken this policy for
40 years then you will not have to do any checking,
you will not have to make any payment from your pocket.
What is there is childhood year, whereas
after this year you will have to complete it, only after this
neither the company nor the organ donor policy available in both the companies.
Talking about Bijnor, in both the companies
this one year, two year and three year option is
available. There is four percent in Tata's policy,
eight percent on 2 year policy and three year policy. Subscribe The
Channel subscribe our Channel. Talking about mid,
subscribe and in this you can
apply for maximum two children. Width
benefits are not of much use
because the top post withdrawal
is minimum of Rs 2 lakh. One regains consciousness quickly,
such an option is available.
Talking about reversal, in one company the pension
available treatment subscribe maximum 5
lakh, everyone can use it.
In this, modern treatment can now be used.
These conditions are subscribed,
like the appointment of a normal subscribe,
duniya anti and preexisting. Its
waiting period is like your normal
policy. Do
study the policy completely. We hope that
Subscribe to us and
like to select any product. If you
liked the video, we keep bringing such information, so
please like and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for
watching.